In no manner
which would lead one to believe...
(Sheldon:)...that he was covering up feelings
of anguish and betrayal.
(Penny:)-Well, good.
-I'm also pleased to report...
(Sheldon:)...that he's all cried out over you.
(Penny:)He's been crying?
(Sheldon:)Oh, I believe that was something else
I wasn't supposed to mention.
(Penny:)Oh, God. I feel terrible.
Do you have a stomachache too?
(Penny:)No. Why, do you?
(Sheldon:)No.
(Penny:)Why did you ask if I had one too?
(Sheldon:)Just making polite
dinner conversation.
(Sheldon:)Your turn.
(Sheldon:)All right.
(Penny:)So, what's new in your life?
(Sheldon:)Well, my new shoes
are not made for running.
(Penny:)Have you been running?
(Sheldon:)No.
(Sheldon:)It's just a suspicion I have.
(Sheldon:)Mm, mm, mm.